<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Aufiblue Projekte</title><link>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Aufiblue Projekte</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2020 Finn Immerheiser. Hugo Theme Designed by [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 11:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aborea - Attention Werwolf!</title><link>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/011-achtung-werwolf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 11:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/011-achtung-werwolf/</guid><description>Have a nice day to you all and have fun with &amp;ldquo;Aborea - Attention Werewolf!
&amp;ldquo;Aborea - Attention Werewolf!&amp;rdquo; is an extension for the roleplaying game Aborea.
It is about the fact that on the last day of every month some rational beings with a weak immune system become werewolves and try to destroy all life. However, at the beginning of the next month they become normal again and cannot remember anything!</description></item><item><title>Dice cards</title><link>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/010-wuerfelkarten/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 17:24:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/010-wuerfelkarten/</guid><description>Dice cards - What is that? Whoever does not have a certain dice at hand, but needs it to be able to play, can download these alternative &amp;ldquo;dice&amp;rdquo;.
For example, if you need a W6, you can cut out the dice cards with the required numbers and throw them into a container. If you want to throw the dice, reach in without looking and pull out one of the dice cards.</description></item><item><title>Aborea - Zombie Apocalypse Mode!</title><link>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/009-aborea-zombie-apocalypse-mode/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 12:02:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/009-aborea-zombie-apocalypse-mode/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Aborea - Zombie Apocalypse Mode&amp;rdquo; is an expansion for the tabletop role playing game Aborea. It is about a zombie apocalypse on the continent of Palea. A constant fight for survival begins!
Have fun reading and playing!
Aborea - Zombie Apocalypse Mode Character sheet Extension to character sheet Overview of important items My-Adventure sheet Help sheet for creation of creatures Item list (empty) Infection points The files are subject to this licence: &amp;ldquo;Attribution 2.</description></item><item><title>Aufiquest!</title><link>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/008-aufiquest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 12:02:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/008-aufiquest/</guid><description>Good day!
Now, after &amp;ldquo;Caterpillars&amp;rdquo;, my second own table role play is ready! It is kept short and therefore easy to learn.
Have fun with it!
Aufiquest - The roleplaying game Character sheet Extension to the caracter sheet Overview of important items Item list (empty) Castle Coins Castle Coins Banknotes 5 Castle Coins Banknotes 10 Castle Coins Banknotes 20 Castle Coins Banknotes 50 Castle Coins Banknotes 100 Castle Coins Banknotes 200 Castle Coins Banknotes 500 Castle Coins Banknotes Blank The files are subject to this licence: &amp;ldquo;Attribution 2.</description></item><item><title>Item cards</title><link>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/006-gegenstandskarten/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 21:03:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/006-gegenstandskarten/</guid><description>I have designed some templates for item cards and offer them here for download.
Item cards create yourself Food cards - back Drinking water cards - back Weapon cards close combat - back Weapon cards ranged combat - back Armour Cards - back The files are subject to this licence: &amp;ldquo;Attribution 2.0 Germany (CC BY 2.0 DE)&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Spielhilfen für Aborea</title><link>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/007-aborea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 21:02:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/007-aborea/</guid><description>I have developed some character sheets etc. for the table role playing game Aborea and put them here for download.
Alternative character sheet Extension to the character sheet Overview of important items Alternative My-Adventure sheet Help sheet for creature creation Item list (empty) The files are subject to this licence: &amp;ldquo;Attribution 2.0 Germany (CC BY 2.0 DE)&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Dice chips</title><link>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/005-wuerfelchips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 21:02:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/005-wuerfelchips/</guid><description>Dice chips - What is that? If you don&amp;rsquo;t have a certain dice at hand, but need it to be able to play, you can download these alternative &amp;ldquo;dice&amp;rdquo;.
For example, if you need a W6, you can cut out the dice chips with the required numbers and throw them into a container. If you want to throw the dice, you reach in without looking and pull out one of the dice chips.</description></item><item><title>Caterpillars!</title><link>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/004-raupen/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 22:04:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/004-raupen/</guid><description>Good day!
Now my first own roleplaying game is finished! It is kept short and therefore easy to learn.
Have fun with it!
Caterpillars - The roleplaying game Character sheet Extension to the character sheet Overview of important items Item list (empty) Rappel The files are subject to this licence: &amp;ldquo;Attribution 2.0 Germany (CC BY 2.0 DE)&amp;rdquo;
Version history Caterpillars - The Roleplaying Game: Version 1.0 - First Version</description></item><item><title>Your fanworks</title><link>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/003-fanwerk-downloads/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:12:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/003-fanwerk-downloads/</guid><description>Hello!
An offer: Feel free to contact me, send me your own extensions and pen and paper roleplaying games -whichever- as files and I will immortalize them here under your name as long as they are not sexist or racist and do not hurt anyone.</description></item><item><title>Other playing aids</title><link>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/002-sonstige-spielhilfen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 12:41:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/002-sonstige-spielhilfen/</guid><description>Hello, here I exhibit at irregular intervals various unordered playing aids for the table role play. These I offer for download.
Portrait sheet Stop!-Cards Stop!-Cards printer frendly The files are subject to this licence: &amp;ldquo;Attribution 2.0 Germany (CC BY 2.0 DE)&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>My first Post</title><link>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/001-new-post/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 20:04:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/001-new-post/</guid><description>Me, that is Aufiblue, invent and develop pen and paper role playing games. There is still a lot planned! Me and my technical support named Martin have been working a lot on this website. It is much more flexible than the old one and I have much more room for manoeuvre. Now I even have a blog and can write entries! This would hardly have been possible on the old site.</description></item><item><title>Data protection</title><link>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/000-datenschutz/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 20:04:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/000-datenschutz/</guid><description>Privacy policy Introduction With the following data protection declaration, we would like to inform you which types of your personal data (hereinafter also referred to as &amp;ldquo;data&amp;rdquo;) we process, for which purposes and to what extent. The data protection declaration applies to all processing of personal data carried out by us, both in the context of providing our services and, in particular, on our websites, in mobile applications and within external online presences, such as our social media profiles (hereinafter also referred to collectively as &amp;ldquo;online offer&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>Imprint</title><link>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/000-impressum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 20:04:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.aufiblue.de/en/blog/000-impressum/</guid><description>Imprint Information according to § 5 TMG Finn Immerheiser
Blücherstrasse 14
26603 Aurich
Represented by:
Martin Jahr Contact us:
Phone: 0170-371 66 36 E-mail: martin@anfinema.de Responsible for the content according to § 55 Abs. 2 RStV: Martin Jahr
Blücherstrasse 14
26603 Aurich
Disclaimer of liability Liability for contents The contents of our pages were created with the greatest care. However, we cannot guarantee the accuracy, completeness and topicality of the contents.</description></item></channel></rss>